<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Anxiety Questionnaire</string>
    <string name="titleString">GAD-7 Screening Questions</string>
    <string name="finalScoreSemicolonString">Final score: </string>
    <string name="missedQuestion1">You did not answer Question 1. Please answer all questions in the GAD-7 section.</string>
    <string name="missedQuestion2">You did not answer Question 2. Please answer all questions in the GAD-7 section.</string>
    <string name="missedQuestion3">You did not answer Question 3. Please answer all questions in the GAD-7 section.</string>
    <string name="missedQuestion4">You did not answer Question 4. Please answer all questions in the GAD-7 section.</string>
    <string name="missedQuestion5">You did not answer Question 5. Please answer all questions in the GAD-7 section.</string>
    <string name="missedQuestion6">You did not answer Question 6. Please answer all questions in the GAD-7 section.</string>
    <string name="missedQuestion7">You did not answer Question 7. Please answer all questions in the GAD-7 section.</string>
    <string name="missedQuestion8">You did not answer Question 8. Please answer all questions in the GAD-7 section.</string>
    <string name="overLastTwoWeeksString">Over the last 2 weeks, how often have you been bothered by the following problems?</string>
    <string name="question1String">1. Feeling nervous, anxious, or on edge</string>
    <string name="notAtAllString">Not at all</string>
    <string name="severalDaysString">Several days</string>
    <string name="moreThanHalfString">More than half the days</string>
    <string name="nearlyEveryDayString">Nearly every day</string>
    <string name="question2String">2. Not being able to stop or control worrying</string>
    <string name="question3String">3. Worrying too much about different things</string>
    <string name="question4String">4. Trouble relaxing</string>
    <string name="question5String">5. Being so restless that it’s hard to sit still</string>
    <string name="question6String">6. Becoming easily annoyed or irritable</string>
    <string name="question7String">7. Feeling afraid as if something awful might happen</string>
    <string name="question8String">8. If you checked off any problems, how difficult have these problems made it for you
to do your work, take care of things at home, or get along with other people?</string>
    <string name="notDifficultString">Not at all difficult</string>
    <string name="somewhatDifficultString">Somewhat difficult</string>
    <string name="veryDifficultString">Very difficult</string>
    <string name="extremelyDifficultString">Extremely difficult</string>
    <string name="personalWellnessTitleString">Personal Wellness (check all that apply)</string>
    <string name="check1String">I know my biggest stress triggers.</string>
    <string name="check2String">I have someone to talk to or a place to write things down, when my stress level is high.</string>
    <string name="check3String">I eat a variety of foods and get the nutrients I need. I have healthy food on hand.</string>
    <string name="check4String">There have been no major changes in my appetite lately.</string>
    <string name="check5String">I participate in some type of physical activity.</string>
    <string name="check6String">I am getting adequate sleep. There have been no major changes in my sleep habits lately.</string>
    <string name="check7String">I am taking my medication as prescribed. I know what to expect from my medication.</string>
    <string name="check8String">I am involved in social activities.</string>
    <string name="check9String">My friends are aware of my needs, and I am considerate of theirs.</string>
    <string name="check10String">I have educated my family and loved ones about my illness to the best of my ability.</string>
    <string name="check11String">I have a job, hobby or volunteer activity where I feel comfortable. It does not cause too much stress, and I am using and improving my skills.</string>
    <string name="lastQuestionHintString">Last question: Describe one way you engage in self-care</string>
    <string name="submitString">Submit</string>
    <string name="resetString">Reset</string>
    <string name="emailCheckString">(Optional) Check to email a copy of your questionnaire to yourself or your counselor when you click SUBMIT.</string>
    <string name="personalWellnessCheckedString">Personal Wellness (checked):</string>
    <string name="personalWellnessUncheckedString">Personal Wellness (unchecked):</string>
    <string name="belowThresholdString">Your score is below the threshold score for mild anxiety.</string>
    <string name="mildAnxietyString">Your score indicates mild anxiety.</string>
    <string name="moderateAnxietyString">Your score indicates moderate anxiety. Please seek further evaluation.</string>
    <string name="severeAnxietyString">Your score indicates severe anxiety. Please seek further evaluation.</string>
    <string name="sendMailString">Send mail…</string>
    <string name="noEmailClientsAvailable">There are no email clients installed.</string>
</resources>
